doridro.com 2008-12-17

# come To || Doridro.Com || :: You Are In: : Wel

---  
**You need to upgrade your Flash Player**  
---  
**Doridro Privacy Policy**  
Who do they apply to  
Are these privacy policies likely to change  
Privacy Policy Statement  
How does administration use the information you provide?  
What about security?  
Why does this website record IP Addresses?  
What are cookies and why does this website use them?  
What about other Websites?  
What is spam and does administration send it?  
Federal Privacy Act  

Doridro Privacy Policy  
---  
**Who do they apply to**  
Everyone, nobody is excused from them, and it is the users responsibilty to keep up to date with changes to the privacy policy.  
Back to top  
**Are these privacy policies likely to change**  
Yes, the privacy policy may be changed as a requirement of Federal and/or State Laws.  
Back to top  
**Privacy Policy Statement**  
The administrator understands that you are concerned about your privacy. Thats why administration has created this privacy policy statement, to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy.  
Back to top  
**How does administration use the information you provide?**  
Administration uses the information you provide to target and personalise the emails we send to you and the offers we make available to you. We do this to ensure that you only receive relevant and appropriate information. administration will not sell or give away your personal information to any other person, company or organisation, unless, it is required by law, or you expressly agree to us giving out your information. Demographic and profile data is only shared with administration affilliates and advertisers on an aggregate or collective basis. However, we will never tell our affilliates your name, your postal address or your email address and other such information.  
Back to top  
**What about security?**  
Administration has modern and robust security measures in place to protect the information you give to us from loss, misuse and alteration. We are constantly reviewing and upgrading these security measures to ensure the very best of protection to you.  
Back to top  
**Why does this website record IP Addresses?**  
When a user joins this website, our computers may record their IP address. In the event that we detect fraud or abuse of our program on our Web site and computers, we may use the IP address of the offender to take action against them. Ultimately this ensures greater protection for you and your personal information.  
Back to top  
**What are cookies and why does this website use them?**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s computer hard drive, containing information about that user. A cookie can only be accessed across the Internet by the website that placed it there. Cookies are used by the website to add functionality and security. You may choose to reject a cookie that this website attempts to place on your computer, however you may then be limited in your use of some areas of the Web site. The use of cookies in this way is wide-spread and commonly accepted by the Internet community.  
Back to top  
**What about other Websites?**  
This website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our website and to read the privacy statements of other websites that you use. This privacy statement applies only to websites owned and operated by the adminstrator of this site.  
Back to top  
**What is spam and does administration send it?**  
The widely accepted definition of SPAM is unsolicited commercial email, or in other words, email of a commercial nature that the recipient does not want. administration does not send SPAM. If you have received unwanted email sent from administration, or purporting to be sent from administration, please contact administration. If you have any questions about the privacy and permission practices of the administration website or your dealings with administration, please contact administration. We are committed to being of service to you and resolving any issues that may arise.  
Back to top  
**Federal Privacy Act**  
This websites Privacy Policy must be read in conjunction with the Federal Privacy Act   
Back to top  

All times are GMT - 5 Hours

****
